Number two, make good choices.
Follow our super handy decision making guide.
This will help you with any decision,
but will also help you make the best career choice for you.
Start by defining the decision you have to make.
In this case, what career to plan for, then establish your criteria.
That's what's important to you in a job.
Next, identify the options of most interest to you,
and then evaluate those options based on your criteria.
Finally, make a decision.
You can always reassess and change course as you go.
But following these steps will help put your priorities in focus
and make the best decision you can.
Career tip number three, get out and volunteer.